

BaldurArge Multimedia Designer

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Baldur Arge Sveinsson, a 25 years old from Iceland, but currently live in Odense Denmark. My passion is web and application development and design, but I love every aspect of design and art. I spend my free time creating, everything from building and designing furniture, painting or making digital art.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

 Icelandic
 •
 •
 •

 English
 •
 •
 •

 Faroese
 •
 •
 •

 Danish
 •
 •
 •

CONTACT ME

+45 60 90 78 14

baldurargesveins@gmail.com

www.baldura.com

https://www.behance.net/baldurargec048

5000 Odense

EDUCATION

2016 - Present Lillebaelt Academy Odense - University of applied sciences

Field of study: Multimedia design and communication

2013 - 2015 Technical College Reykjavík

Field of study: Diploma Computer Study Programme.

B

Matriculation examination from vocational - and artistic

study programmes

WORK EXPERIENCE _____

2016 Slippbarinn

Bartender at one of the top rated cocktail bars in Iceland

2013 - 2016 The National Theatre of Iceland

Worked backstage during live shows and building stage sets

and props.

Summers Klettur

2012-2016 Both as an employee and part time manager

for a tire storage.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS _____



Adobe illustrator Adobe InDesign Sketch Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom Adobe After Effects



HTML / CSS
Javascript
PHP
AngularJs
C#
Python
MeteorJs
Mysql / MongoDB